List<Map> technicalAnalysis = [
  {
    'question':
        'What does the term "support level" refer to in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'The price level where buying interest is sufficiently strong to overcome selling pressure.',
      'The highest price level reached by a stock during a specific period.',
      'The price level where selling interest is sufficiently strong to overcome buying pressure.',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is a common indicator used to identify trends in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'Moving Average',
      'Earnings Per Share (EPS)',
      'Price-to-Earnings (P/E) Ratio',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the Relative Strength Index (RSI) measure?',
    'options': [
      'The speed of price movements',
      'Market volatility',
      'Overbought or oversold conditions',
    ],
    'answer': 2,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is a "candlestick" in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'A type of financial instrument',
      'A visual representation of price movements within a specific time period',
      'A type of dividend payment made to shareholders',
    ],
    'answer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What does the term "resistance level" mean in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'The price level where buying interest is sufficiently strong to overcome selling pressure.',
      'The highest price level reached by a stock during a specific period.',
      'The price level where selling interest is sufficiently strong to overcome buying pressure.',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which pattern is often interpreted as a reversal signal in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'Cup and Handle',
      'Bullish Engulfing',
      'Hanging Man',
    ],
    'answer': 1,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the purpose of using trendlines in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'To identify support and resistance levels',
      'To predict future earnings of a company',
      'To calculate the dividend yield',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the term "volume" represent in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'The number of shares traded in a given period',
      'The price of a single share',
      'The market capitalization of a company',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which indicator measures the momentum of a stock\'s price movement?',
    'options': [
      'MACD (Moving Average Convergence Divergence)',
      'PE Ratio (Price-to-Earnings Ratio)',
      'NAV (Net Asset Value)',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the term "breakout" signify in technical analysis?',
    'options': [
      'When a stock\'s price moves above a resistance level',
      'When a stock\'s price moves below a support level',
      'When a stock splits into multiple shares',
    ],
    'answer': 0,
  },
];

List<String> correctResponses = [
  "Correct!",
  "Well done!",
  "You're on fire!",
  "Fantastic!",
  "You nailed it!",
  "Brilliant!",
  "Excellent choice!",
  "You got it right!",
  "Superb!",
  "Amazing!",
];
List<String> wrongResponses = [
  "Wrong!",
  "Wrong Answer :(",
  "Hard luck.",
  "Oops! Don't worry, let's try again.",
  "Hmm, not quite there. You've got this!",
  "Uh-oh! Keep going, you'll get it next time!",
  "Not quite, but you're getting closer!",
  "That's not it, but keep trying!",
  "Hmm, not the one, but you're learning!",
  "Close, but not quite! Keep pushing!"
];
